[Newsletter  
Sign-up](https://www.gatewayfestivalorchestra.org/newsletter-sign-up/)

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

###### **Gateway Festival Orchestra**

###### **Privacy Policy**

###### _Effective as of May 10, 2021_

###### **Introduction**

###### The Gateway Festival Orchestra (“GFO,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) respects the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us in using our website (“Site”) and the services provided through our Site (collectively, “Services”).    

###### From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will post an amended version on this webpage. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically. 

###### This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:

###### [**1.**      **Collecting and Using Information**](#_Toc68675625)

###### [**2.**      **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**](#_Toc68675626)

###### [**3.**      **Third Party Processors**](#_Toc68675627)

###### [**4.**      **“Do Not Track” Signals**](#_Toc68675628)

###### [**5.**      **Choices About Your Personally Identifiable Information**](#_Toc68675629)

###### [**6.**      **Security**](#_Toc68675630)

###### [**7.**      **Third Party Links**](#_Toc68675631)

###### [**8.**      **Children’s Privacy**](#_Toc68675632)

###### [**9.**      **Notice to California Residents**](#_Toc68675633)

###### [**10.**        **How to Contact Us**](#_Toc68675634)

###### **1.**      **Collecting and Using Information**

###### **Personally Identifiable Information We Collect Online**

###### We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you through your use of the Site and Services. “Personally Identifiable Information” is individually identifiable information about an individual consumer that we collect online and that we maintain in an accessible form. We collect the following types of Personally Identifiable Information:

###### _Information You Provide_

###### We may collect the following Personally Identifiable Information that you voluntarily provide to us:

* ###### _Sign Up for Newsletter._ To sign up for our newsletter, Sostenuto, you will provide us with your email address.
    
* ###### _Donate._ To make a donation online, you will provide us with your name and email address and then you will be redirected to PayPal’s website to complete the transaction. PayPal’s privacy policy is available [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). We do not collect or receive the financial information provided to PayPal.
    
* ###### _Get Email Reminders._ To sign up for concert and event email reminders, you will provide us with your email address.
    
* ###### _Contact Us._ To contact us, you will provide us with your name, email address, and any other Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to provide.

###### _Information as You Navigate Our Site_

###### We automatically collect certain Personally Identifiable Information through your use of the Site and Services, such as the following:

* ###### _Usage Information_. We collect information such as which of the pages on the Site you access, the frequency of access, and what you click on while on the Site.
    
* ###### _Device Information._ We collect information about the device you are using, such as hardware model, operating system, application version number, and browser.
    
* ###### _Mobile Device Information_. In addition to the Device Information listed above, when you access our Site via a browser on your mobile device, we collect and aggregate information about whether you are accessing the Site via a mobile device or tablet, device type, and carrier.
    
* ###### _Location Information_. We collect location information from Site visitors on a city-regional basis.

###### _Third Party Information_

###### In some cases, we may receive certain Personally Identifiable Information from you about a third party. For example, you may provide the email address of a third party to receive the GFO newsletter. If you submit any Personally Identifiable Information about another individual to us, you are responsible for making sure that you have the authority to do so and to allow us to use their Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

###### **How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information**

###### We use the Personally Identifiable Information we collect to provide the Services to you, to improve our Services and Site, and to protect our legal rights. In addition, we may use the Personally Identifiable Information we collect to:

* ###### Email you our newsletter;
    
* ###### Email you concert and event reminders;
    
* ###### Collect and process donations;
    
* ###### Call you to promote special events, last minute changes or cancellations, or special offers. Customers will only receive calls from us if they provide us with their telephone numbers. If you wish to be removed from receiving calls, please notify us at [info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org](mailto:info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org%20) or 314-741-5948.
    
* ###### Communicate with you about our Site or Services or to inform you of any changes to our Site or Services; 
    
* ###### Provide support; 
    
* ###### Maintain and improve our Site and Services;
    
* ###### Defend our legal rights and the rights of others;
    
* ###### Efficiently maintain our business; and
    
* ###### Comply with applicable law. 

###### **How We Share Your Personally Identifiable Information**

###### We may share the information that we collect about you in the following ways:

* ###### With service providers who perform data or Site-related services on our behalf (e.g., email, hosting, maintenance, backup, analysis, etc.);
    
* ###### To the extent that we are required to do so by law;
    
* ###### In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
    
* ###### To establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights, including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention;
    
* ###### To any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that Personally Identifiable Information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that Personally Identifiable Information;
    
* ###### To any other person or entity as part of any business or asset sale, equity transaction, merger, acquisition or in preparation for any of these events; and
    
* ###### To any other person or entity where you consent to the disclosure.

###### **2.**      **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

###### **How We Use Cookies**

###### Like many other companies, we use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as pixels and web beacons) (collectively, “Cookies”). “Cookies” are small files of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer hard drive, mobile or other devices (e.g., smartphones or tablets).

###### We use Cookies to:

* ###### Estimate audience size and usage patterns;
    
* ###### Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions to resolve issues and offer better site experiences and tools in the future; and

###### We set some Cookies ourselves and others are set by other entities. We use Cookies set by other entities to provide us with useful information to help us improve our Site and Services, to conduct advertising, and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising. For example, we use Cookies from Google and Facebook.  

###### **How You Can Opt-Out of Cookies**

###### _Browser Settings_

###### Cookies can be blocked by changing your Internet browser settings to refuse all or some Cookies. If you choose to block all Cookies (including essential Cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the Site.

###### You can find out more about Cookies and how to manage them by visiting [www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

###### _Platform Controls_ 

###### You can opt out of Cookies set by specific entities by following the instructions found at these links:

* ###### Google: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/)
    
* ###### Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/about/ads](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads)

###### _Advertising Industry Resources_

###### You can understand which entities have currently enabled Cookies for your browser or mobile device and how to opt-out of some of those Cookies by accessing the [Network Advertising Initiative’s website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/). For more information on mobile specific opt-out choices, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Mobile Choices website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices).

###### Please note that these opt-out mechanisms are specific to the device or browser on which they are exercised. Therefore, you will need to opt out on every browser and device that you use.

###### **Google Analytics**

###### We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses Cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with the Site and Services, compile reports on their activity, and provide other services related to their activity and usage. The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a returning visitor, and any referring website. The technologies used by Google Analytics do not gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s [privacy policies](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt-out of tracking of analytics by Google, click [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

###### **Google reCAPTCHA**

###### We use Google reCAPTCHA, a free service provided by Google, Inc., to protect our Site from spam and abuse. Google reCAPTCHA uses advanced risk analysis techniques to decipher humans and bots. Google reCAPTCHA works differently depending on what version is deployed. For example, you may be asked to check a box indicating that you are not a robot or Google reCAPTCHA may detect abusive traffic without user interaction. Google reCAPTCHA works by transmitting certain types of information to Google, such as the referrer URL, IP address, visitor behavior, operating system information, browser and length of the visit, cookies, and mouse movements. Your use of Google reCAPTCHA is subject to Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Use](https://policies.google.com/terms). More information as to Google reCAPTCHA and how it works is available [here](https://developers.google.com/recaptcha).

###### **3.**      **Third Party Processors**

###### To ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information receives an adequate level of protection, we have put in place appropriate procedures with the service providers we share it with to ensure that it is treated consistent with applicable data security and privacy laws.  For example, we use PayPal as a payment processor.

###### **4.**       **“Do Not Track” Signals**

###### Some internet browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Given that there is not a uniform way that browsers communicate the “Do Not Track” signal, the Site does not currently interpret, respond to or alter its practices when it receives “Do Not Track” signals.

###### **5.**      **Choices About Your Personally Identifiable Information**

###### **Review and Request Changes to Your Personally Identifiable Information**

###### To review or request changes to any of your Personally Identifiable Information, please contact us at [info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org](mailto:info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org).

###### **Marketing Communications**

###### To unsubscribe from our newsletter or concert email reminders, please click the unsubscribe link included in the footer of our emails. You also may submit a request to us at [info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org](mailto:info@gatewayfestivalorchestra.org).

###### **6.**      **Security**

###### We maintain commercially reasonable security measures to protect the Personally Identifiable Information we collect and store from loss, misuse, destruction, or unauthorized access.  However, no security measure or modality of data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.  Although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.

###### **7.**      **Third Party Links**

###### The Site may contain links that will let you leave the Site and access another website. Linked websites are not under our control. This Privacy Policy applies solely to Personally Identifiable Information that is acquired by us on this Site. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

###### **8.**      **Children’s Privacy**

###### The Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under 13.

###### **9.**      **Notice to California Residents**

###### We do not disclose personal information obtained through our Site or Services to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Accordingly, we have no obligations under California Civil Code § 1798.83.

* Gateway Festival Orchestra  
    PO Box 50211  
    St. Louis MO, 63105

501(c)(3)     EIN: 430815081

* © 2024 Gateway Festival Orchestra
